<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>feralhosting.github.io</title>
    <description>Thing FAQ and wiki related.</description>
    <link>feralhosting.github.io</link>
    <atom:link href="feralhosting.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Front page</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/OBCzjyQ.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; Hello,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the home for a lot of the attached content in the feralhosting.com FAQs. This is basically a hosting platform for the images,scripts,snippets and more. It is centralised and easy to manage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current FAQs are formatted in form of bbcode. One goal of this repo was, and is, to port the existing FAQs to markdown. Markdown is a bit more portable and lets you format large bodies of text reasonably quickly. For this purpose two tools have been created convert a specific format of:  bbcode &gt; markdown and markdown &gt; bbcode . If correct formatting is used when creating one or the other the tool should be able to convert the critical tags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This github user, feralhosting and associated repositories are purely an endeavour to improve and manage the FAQ and wiki. A lot of the content is user generated and does not fall within the direct support requirements of the staff. So this means that checking and updating some of these FAQs in not on the top of their list of priorities. Having these repositories allows progress to be made, tracked and continued. Especially where things like images and scripts are hosted in less than desirable ways that are not friendly to the long term integrity of the articles. It has allowed me to centralise and track the work that has been done so far to create, improve or archive the current FAQs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also the home to certain projects unique to the feralhosting.com slot setup.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>feralhosting.github.io/front%20page/2013/05/29/Front-page/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">feralhosting.github.io/front%20page/2013/05/29/Front-page/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>